[{
        "question": "How many vowels are there in Korean language?",
        "answer": "10",
        "choices": [
            "5",
            "10",
            "21",
            "14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many simple consonants are there in Korean language?",
        "answer": "14",
        "choices": [
            "5",
            "10",
            "21",
            "14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㅂ”?",
        "answer": "b",
        "choices": [
            "p",
            "k",
            "b",
            "g"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㄱ”?",
        "answer": "g",
        "choices": [
            "g",
            "d",
            "m",
            "j"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㅊ”?",
        "answer": "ch",
        "choices": [
            "d",
            "s",
            "j",
            "ch"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㅁ”?",
        "answer": "m",
        "choices": [
            "m",
            "b",
            "p",
            "k"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㄴ”?",
        "answer": "n",
        "choices": [
            "k",
            "n",
            "p",
            "s"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㅈ”?",
        "answer": "j",
        "choices": [
            "k",
            "j",
            "p",
            "s"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㄷ”?",
        "answer": "d",
        "choices": [
            "k",
            "b",
            "p",
            "d"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following english characters corresponds to “ㄹ”?",
        "answer": "r",
        "choices": [
            "r",
            "b",
            "p",
            "s"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ways are there to write a block?",
        "answer": "4",
        "choices": [
            "2",
            "5",
            "1",
            "4"
        ]
    }
]